peugeot
peugeot
yes good afternoon hello a couple of days
да добрый день привет своих пары дней
ago we talked with you
назад общались с вами
yes well maybe it was six controversial
да ну может было шесть спорный
to talk about hotel praha I’m
поговорить про hotel praha мне
more interested in the ferret we were
интереснее про хорька мы с вами там
talking about kharkov
разговаривали про харьков
Russian regrouping yes they
перегруппировку российскую да они с вами
have already talked to you a lot with whom now tell me
уже много с кем говорил вот расскажите
to watch from 6 can  revise the entries in
смотреть с 6 могу пересмотреть записи в
it tell me to open it and this is how you feel
ней расскажи раскрыть и мне вот как вы
about the fact that the shameful Russian troops
относитесь к тому что российские войска
fled from the Kharkov region,
позорного бежали из харьковской области
you know, I’ll kill you a broken look to find a
вы знаете я разбитую вам вид убью найти
fresh entry called
свежую запись называется
russia criticize the authorities to whom this
россия критикуют власти кому так
is called this time two
называется это раза рассуждают два
American analysts argue in August
американских аналитика вот августе
it will be clear to the pirates  if you know the low ones,
пиратам будет понятно если вам низкие
look there the whole thing
знаете посмотрите там все это дело
is explained briefly how such a powerful
объясняется коротко как как такая мощная
superpower received a star from the Ukrainians,
сверхдержава от украинцев получила
but you can say all the
звездюлей но вы можете говорить всего
ropes were cleared like that, I wo
канатов прочистили такой я не буду
n’t explain to you on an hour, I
часовая вам объясню где-то
really love it and look
коротко на самом деле любит и посмотрите
there for minutes your collective is not higher
там минут ваше коллективное не выше
come when you have your opinion
приходите когда у вас есть свое мнение
why t  how did it happen, I already answered you,
почему так случилось я вам уже ответил
well, why did Russia come here to the
а хорошо а зачем сюда россия заходила в
Kharkiv region
харьковскую область
did the Americans write or not they didn’t write there, they argue from the topic
они не написали там рассуждают от темы
listen, it will be useful for you to enlighten
послушайте вам будет полезно просветить
the cops from the felt boots the
из валенка ментам
Americans with the Americans cheating the mouse on the
американцы с американцами обмана мыши на
Americans I’m at 10 analysts
американцы я на 10 аналитики
drying to listen to them but  tell
просушки послушать их но расскажите
briefly what the media say.  analysts about the
коротко что говорят сми . аналитики об
retreat of the Russian army to the shameful
отступлении российской армии позорному
flight left so much equipment for the
бегству оставили столько техники визу
Foreign Ministry’s visa, few people
мида это мало человек
retold this, they
этом пересказывал
will remain smoking for two minutes, you
останутся курите вы две минуты мне
tell me that you looked, I could take 2-3
говорите что посмотрели возьму могли 2-3
sentences, the essence, I tell you for two minutes
предложения суть я вам две минуты говорю
that I won’t talk about the topic, but I sold it for
что на тему говорить не буду а продал за
why what happens  when drying, they don’t want
почему что случается при сушке не хотят
to talk about this topic, I told you to
на эту тему говорить я вам сказал
listen in a tank and
послушайте танком и подробности
explain the details, she specifically chooses connections to Ukraine
объясняться она связи в украину
in chat roulette
специально выбираете в чат-рулетке до
until why
для чего
I ask you, I also spoke, but I’m bored now,
я спрошу вас тоже говорил но я сейчас
I’m bored, so I look like it’s
скучно мне скучно поэтому я смотрю как с
fun with Ukrainians if people come
украинцами весело если приходит люди
who are starting to start screaming
которые там и начинают про стала кричать
what else is there to swear there I look at
что там еще там материться я смотрю на
it like a zoo
это как зоопарк
in a special abortion people who
в специальном аборт люди которые с
are bored with whom we communicate on different
которыми скучно мы общаемся на разные на
topics on what topics in the book we communicate with Ukrainians
какие темы на книге мы с украинцами
I just said with the
общаетесь я вот только что он сказал с
previous guy talking about  mountains
предыдущим парнем разговаривали про горы
pro football let's-let's talk to me than
про футбол давайте-давайте со мной чем
35 years ago with a
35 назад разговаривал с
girl so pretty Knife Games  you are with
девушка такая миловидная нож игры со
me in basses the ground and the guy girl trance
мной басами грунт и парень девушка транс
what we will talk about then what do you
чем мы с вами тогда поговорим о чем вы
want to talk about
хотите поговорить о чем
what to ask a question create I wanted to create about the
выше задать вопрос создавать я хотел про
war about the Kharkov region look
войну про харьковскую область выглядите
like you don’t want to talk about this topic I
что вы не хотите при эту тему говорить я
said that the question is on this topic  you
сказал что вопрос по этой теме вам
will be covered in much more detail here in this one I will give you a link look at you high well now let's you
высоким хорошо теперь давайте вы
suggest topics on which you would like to
предлагаете темы по которой вы хотели бы
talk
поговорить
you want me
хотите чтобы я
to give you a very similar one too you came in you
тоже очень такой подбросил вы зашли вы
mean you want to talk about something here with
значит хотите о чем-то пообщаться вот с
someone curses  filthy Tambov
кем-то проклятий поганом тамбов
Kryvyi Rih region Tambov Kryvyi Rih
криворожской область тамбов криворожской
Logos partially built it already
логосе частично уже ее построил этот
restored to the water level
восстановили до уровень воды
stabilized to it your
стабилизировали до его ваш
terrorist act like mined and
террористический акт типа добыл и
restored well and what do you want to
восстановили ну и что что вы хотите этим
say by that you you know something is
сказать вы вы вы знаете что-то
happening on something is happening is
происходит на что-то происходит
flooding to the territory
затапливается до территория
that is, it turns out you are looking at
то есть получается смотрите вы про
Kharkov, the cube of pollution and I don’t want to go
харьков кубу загрязнения и не хочу иди
look there, the general, but here you are still
смотри там генерал а тут вы все-таки
translating  go to military topics
переводите на военные темы
you please look we express asked a
вы радуете смотрите выражаем задали
question the answer to your questions you will find there
вопрос ответ на свои вопросы найдете там
expressed that if you asked what topic
выражал что если вы спросили какую тему
I want to talk to then let them also
хочу поговорить с тогда давайте им тоже
a'laberdy come to give you you wanted
а'лаберды пришли давать вам вы захотели
about Kharkov asked and on skype crooked
про харькова спросил и по skype кривой
horn like what you get  they removed the
рог нравится что получается вы удалили
missiles from afar on the lady and what
ракеты издалека по даме и что
do you think is comparable to the shameful
вы считаете это сравнимо с позорным
flight from Kharkov and the Kharkov
бегством из харькова и харьковской
region, but now look, let's see
области а вот теперь смотрите давайте
why the law does not work in Russia,
так почему в россии не работает закон
why do you have lawless countries, what kind of
почему у вас странам беззакония какой
legality, look yesterday, an hour,
законность вот смотрите вчера час
probably a partner company and gifts
наверное компания-партнёр и дарств
distributed a video  where the handsome
распространила видео где пригожим
head of this private military
руководителя этой частной военной
company in the zones is agitating the law to go
компании в зонах агитирует закон ехать
to the so-called special military
на так называемую специальную военную
operation if they don’t fight for 6 months,
операцию если не 6 месяцев
and then they are released from
воюют да потом они освобождаются от
their criminal term, no matter what it is,
своего срока уголовного какой бы он не
well, where is it written in the law why in
ну где такое в законе прописано почему в
Russia some peasant can come
россии какой-то мужик может приходить
zone jerk
зоны [__]
grandpa turk grandpa you don't say
дедушка турок дедушка вы не говорите то
good for fool  so I ask again,
хорошо за дурак я спрашиваю ещё раз
answer the question you occupied, read out
ответьте на вопрос вы заняли зачитайте
some kind of circus of some zone, trust a
каким-то цирком какой-то зоны доверят
weapon, such as the high technology of
оружие типа ли высокой технологичностью
which is hardly the world of arthur, so already in
которого едва мира артура так уже ужасе
horror there are even your bunnies,
уже плену есть даже зайки ваши вот
well, let's comment on you
хорошо давайте прокомментируете вас
framed life how do you believe fairy tales and
подставили жизнь как ты сказки верить и
let's do it so
давать им сделаем так
cut off that the
срезаете что
war is hard
война тяжелое
in the referendum on days at 5 there is a cleansing on
в референдуме по дни в 5 там очищение в
Saturday to Friday of gases up to 5 cm but for
субботу в пятницу газов до 5 см но за
these five not in that for a referendum with such a
эти пять не в том за референдум с таким
boring baker am among the WTO and the
скучным хлебальник am среди вто и
incident vincent about hockey says yes
инциденте винсент про хоккей говорит да
like with people  something else has passed there
типа с людьми там прошло-то еще
russia russia you don’t have a country the whole
россия россия не у вас нет страны все
country has already
страна уже
collapsed, it still exists by inertia
развалилась она по инерции еще
only because different
существует только потому что разные
clans divide it
кланы делят ее
if you have a law in your country
если у вас в стране есть закон
tell me under what law they
расскажите по какому закону на зайков
take bunnies from the colonies in the army he was a
берут из колоний в армии он был
rapist for example  he
насильником например убийцей его
takes everything so
забирает всё так
-called as a killer, he serves there for six months,
называемое он там полгода служит получая
getting money to drag it out of your budget, in
затащит бабки до из вашего бюджета по
fact,
сути
and six months later he will be
и через полгода его
amnestied or when  yes, I don’t know if
амнистируют или когда я не знаю будет
it will be carried out anywhere in the
это проводить нигде такого в
legislation, no, that is, Russia
законодательстве нет ок то есть россия
is a country of lawlessness where personally they
это страна беззакония где лично им
do anything by Putin’s desire, and
желанием путина делается что угодно а
then these bunnies in six months, all these
потом эти зайки через полгода все эти
killers on a SIM card will massively begin to
убийцы на симке массово начнут
return to Russian cities,
возвращаться в российские города
united so it’s not just everyone  there
сплоченные так уже не просто каждый там
they will already be gathered into gangs
зассе они уже в банды будут собраны
because they won
потому что они выиграли
in this special military operation and
в этой специальной военной операции и
what they will do with you there it will be
что они буду там делать с вами это будет
very very fun therefore Russians checks
очень очень весело поэтому россиян чеки
I am very glad that
я очень рад тому что
Russia is making such stupid steps and
россия делает такие глупые шаги так и
will fall apart faster help to
быстрее быстрее развалится помогайте
break up  Russia
разваливать россии слава украине
glory to ukraine
подписуйтесь на канал ставте лайк